Guide to the A.I.R. Gallery Archives MSS.184
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IV: Photos/slides
  - Subseries J: B-III SLIDE
    - Artist/Event: Diane Samuels / Filing Date: September, 1995; Number of Slides:; ** Member from 1985 - (Box 19, Folder 868)
      Old number: B - III - 1 - (1- )
      Contents: 10 slides
    - Artist/Event: Rochelle Shicoff / Filing Date: September, 1995; Number of Slides:; ** Member from 1985 - (Box 19, Folder 869)
      Old number: B - III - 2 - (1- )
      Contents: 24 slides, 1 outslip: "Rochelle Shicoff"
    - Artist/Event: Sylvia Sleigh / Filing Date: September, 1995; Number of Slides:; ** Member from 1995 - (Box 19, Folder 870)
      Old number: B - III - 3 - (1- )
      Contents: 46 slides
    - Artist/Event: Elizabeth Munro Smith / Filing Date: September, 1995; Number of Slides:; ** Member from 1988 - (Box 19, Folder 871)
      Old number: B - III - 4 - (1- )
      Contents: 160 slides, 1 outslip: "Elizabeth Monroe[sic] Smith"
    - Artist/Event: Nancy Spero / Filing Date: September, 1995; Number of Slides: / ** Member from 1972 - (Box 19, Folder 872)
      Old number: B - III - 5 - (1- )
      Contents: 62 slides
    - Artist/Event: Barbara Takenaga / Filing Date: September, 1995; Number of Slides: / ** Member from 1988 - (Box 19, Folder 873)
      Old number: B - III - 6 - (1- )
      Contents: 12 slides, 1 outslip: "Barbara Takenaga 1987"
    - Artist/Event: Clover Vail / Filing Date: September, 1995; Number of Slides: / ** Member from 1978 - (Box 19, Folder 874)
      Old number: B - III - 7 - (1- )
      Contents: 27 slides, 1 outslip: "Clover Vail 1988"
    - Artist/Event: Susan L. Williams / Member from 1972 - (Box 19, Folder 875)
      Old number: B - III - 8 - (1- )
      Contents: 2 slides, 1 outslip: "Susan Williams Watermill 72"
  - Subseries K: B-IV SLIDE
    - Artist/Event:"CHOICE" --December 10, 1991 - January 4, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 876)
      Old number: B - IV - 1 - (1- )
      Contents: 26 slides (re-sleeved: 2nd sheet has "MAY" written, both sheets have stickers reading "12/10, 1991-1/4, 1992" and "CHOICE")
    - Artist/Event: Barbara Takenaga -- October 8 - 26, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 877)
      Old number: B - IV - 2 - (1- )
      Contents: 12 slides
    - Artist/Event: Rachel bas-Cohain -- June 4 - 22, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 878)
      Old number: B - IV - 3 - (1- )
      Contents: 5 slides
    - Artist/Event: Jane Haskell -- April 24 - May 12, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 879)
      Old number: B - IV - 4 - (1- )
      Contents: 20 slides
    - Artist/Event: Sarah Stengle -- February 23 - March 12, 1988 (post-it attached: "Feb 23 - March 12 '88 Artists Choose Artists") (Box 19, Folder 880)
      Old number: B - IV - 5 - (1- )
      Contents: 2 slides
    - Artist/Event: Jane Haskell -- January 12 - 30, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 881)
      Old number: B - IV - 6 - (1- )
    - Artist/Event: 15th Anniversary Exhibition --, 1987 (post-it attached: "Jan 27 - Feb 14, 1987 Group show? Unidentified") (Box 19, Folder 882)
      Old number: B - IV - 7 - (1- )
      Contents: 118 slides, 1 outslip: "Sylvia Sleigh The Court of Pan"
    - Artist/Event: Donna Byars -- March 31 - April 18, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 883)
      Old number: B - IV - 8 - (1- )
      Contents: 23 slides, 1 outslip: "Donna Byars Standing Bear 1988"
    - Artist/Event: Dotty Attie -- October 14 - November 22, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 884)
      Old number: B - IV - 9 - (1- )
      Contents: 17 slides, 1 outslip: "Dotty Attie Why Did She Do It 1985"
    - Artist/Event: A.I.R. Group Show -- October, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 885)
      Old number: B - IV - 10 - (1- )
      Contents: 23 slides, 1 outslip: "A.I.R. Group Show 1985"
    - Artist/Event: Diane Samuels -- June 4 - 22, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 886)
      Old number: B - IV - 11 - (1- )
      Contents: 5 slides, 1 outslip: "Diane Samuels"
    - Artist/Event:"Holiday Invitational Show" -- December 19, 1984 - January 5, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 887)
      Old number: B - IV - 12 - (1- )
      Contents: 55 slides
    - Artist/Event: Carla Tardi -- January 10 - 28, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 888)
      Old number: B - IV - 13 - (1- )
      Contents: 3 slides
    - Artist/Event: Barbara Strasen -- November 29 - December 17, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 889)
      Old number: B - IV - 14 - (1- )
    - Artist/Event: Ann[sic] Healy -- March 15 - April 2, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 890)
      Old number: B - IV - 15 - (1- )
      Contents: 4 slides
    - Artist/Event: Louise Kramer -- January 11 - 29, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 891)
      Old number: B - IV - 16 - (1- )
      Contents: 48 slides, 1 outslip: "Louise Kramer 84"
    - Artist/Event: View from Upstate -- June 8 - 26, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 892)
      Old number: B - IV - 17 - (1- )
      Contents: 8 slides
  - Subseries L: B-V SLIDE
    - Artist/Event: Gallery Space + Others (Box 19, Folder 893)
      Old number: B - V - 1 - (1- )
    - Artist/Event: Daria Dorosh (Box 19, Folder 894)
      Old number: B - V - 2 - (1- )
      Contents: 17 slides, 1 outslip: "Daria Dorosh Folded Forms"
    - Artist/Event: Lenore Goldberg (Box 19, Folder 895)
      Old number: B - V - 3 - (1- )
      Contents: NO SLIDES. [slide sleeve empty when collection was accessioned.] 1 outslip: "Lenore Goldberg Untitled '87"
    - Artist/Event: Louise Kramer (Box 19, Folder 896)
      Old number: B - V - 4 - (1- )
    - Artist/Event: Nancy Storrow (Box 19, Folder 897)
      Old number: B - V - 5 - (1- )
      Contents: 7 slides
    - Artist/Event: Carolyn Martin / Member from 1988 - (Box 19, Folder 898)
    - Artist/Event: Carol Ross / Member from 1988 - (Box 19, Folder 899)
      Contents: 1 slide
    - Artist/Event: Elke Solomon / Member from 1984 - (Box 19, Folder 900)
    - Artist/Event: Carol Kumata (Box 19, Folder 901)
      Contents: 1 photo, 39 slides, 1 outslip
      Photo credit: David L. Smith
    - Artist/Event: Claire Wolf Krantz (Box 19, Folder 902)
      Contents: 22 photos, 175 slides, 1 outslip" "Kranz[sic]"
    - Artist/Event: Adrienne Heinrich (Box 19, Folder 903)
      Contents: 14 photos, 109 slides
      Photo credit: Kathy Buckalew, Georgia Bedrosian
  - Subseries M: B-VI SLIDE
    - Artist/Event: Kim Abeles (Box 20, Folder 904)
    - Artist/Event: Barbara Berk (Box 20, Folder 905)
    - Artist/Event: Barbara Garber (Box 20, Folder 906)
    - Artist/Event: Jane Gilmor (Box 20, Folder 907)
    - Artist/Event: Lorraine Archacki (Box 20, Folder 908)
      Contents: 6 slides
    - Artist/Event: Gerda Meyer Bernstein (Box 20, Folder 909)
      Contents: 12 slides, 1 outslip: "Gerda Meyer Bernstein Requiem"
    - Artist/Event: Marcia Godosky (Box 20, Folder 910)
    - Artist/Event: Ursula Kavanagh (Box 20, Folder 911)
    - Artist/Event: Suzanne Olmsted (Box 20, Folder 912)
    - Artist/Event: Maggie Poor (Box 20, Folder 913)
      Contents: 2 slides, 1 outslip: "Maggie Poor 118 Sullivan St. New York NY 10012 212-966-2148"; post-it note attached: "M. Poor Re: Holiday Invitational Backroom Show"
    - Artist/Event: Jon Reis (Box 20, Folder 914)
      Contents: 16 slides
    - Artist/Event: Kathleen Schneider (Box 20, Folder 915)
    - Artist/Event: M. Weidner (Box 20, Folder 916)
    - Artist/Event: Jean Kondo Weigl (Box 20, Folder 917)
  - Subseries N: B-VII SLIDE
    - Artist/Event: National Affiliate Members Show -- September 12-30, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 918)
      Contents: 1 slide, 1 outslip: "National Affiliate 1995"
    - Artist/Event: Blue Angel -- March 15 - April 2, 1988 -- curated by Juli Carson + Howard McCalebb (Box 20, Folder 919)
    - Artist/Event: Alice Attie (Box 20, Folder 920)
    - Artist/Event: Constance Merriman (Box 20, Folder 921)
      Contents: 2 photos, 183 slides, 1 outslip: "Merriman"
    - Artist/Event: Mary Maughelli (Box 20, Folder 922)
      Contents: 17 photos, 129 slides, 1 outslip: "Maughelli"
  - Subseries O: B-VIII
    - Artist/Event: Nancy Azara (Box 20, Folder 923)
      Contents: 107 slides, 1 post-it: "slides missing: 1. Gold Shaman 1987 2. Young Goddess 3. Old Goddess"
    - Artist/Event: Gerda Meyer Bernstein (Box 20, Folder 924)
      Contents: 53 slides
    - Artist/Event: Leila Daw (Box 20, Folder 925)
      Contents: 118 slides, 2 outslips: "Documentation of Prehistoric River Channel sky project; Skywriting smoke mapping ancient channel of Mississippi through present flood plain" and "Documentation of Making the Invisible Visible sky project; Parallel lines of skywriting smoke drawn over confluence of Illinois + Mississippi Rivers for interaction with air currents"
    - Artist/Event: Jane Gilmor (Box 20, Folder 926)
      Contents: 136 slides, 7 photonegatives
    - Artist/Event: Juri Kim (Box 20, Folder 927)
      Contents: 73 slides
    - Artist/Event: Elke Solomon (Box 20, Folder 928)
      Contents: 104 slides, 1 outslip: "Untitled (2 Parts) Drawing Center"
  - Subseries P: B-IX SLIDE
    - Artist/Event: Liz Surbeck Biddle (Box 20, Folder 929)
      Contents: 19 slides
    - Artist/Event: Ivy Dachman (Box 20, Folder 930)
    - Artist/Event: Jessie Nebraska Gifford (Box 20, Folder 931)
      Contents: 102 slides, 1 outslip: "J. Nebraska Gifford 94"
    - Artist/Event: Tanya Hartman (Box 20, Folder 932)
      Contents: 89 slides
    - Artist/Event: Sue Hettmansperger (Box 20, Folder 933)
      Contents: 72 slides, 29 photonegatives
    - Artist/Event: Ursula Kavanagh (Box 20, Folder 934)
    - Artist/Event: Mo Neal (Box 20, Folder 935)
    - Artist/Event: Rebecca Seeman (Box 20, Folder 936)
      Contents: 33 slides, 1 post-it: "exhibition files 82/83 former affiliate"
    - Artist/Event: Georgette Sosin (Box 20, Folder 937)
      Contents: 31 slides
    - Artist/Event: Jean Kondo Weigl (Box 20, Folder 938)
      Contents: 45 slides, 1 post-it: "former affiliate"
    - Artist/Event: Fay Torres Yap (Box 20, Folder 939)
  - Subseries Q: B-X SLIDE
    - Artist/Event: Ellen McMahon (Box 20, Folder 940)
      Contents: 12 postcards
    - Artist/Event: Jane Greer / May 27 - June 14, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 941)
      Contents: 10 photocopies
    - Artist/Event: Madeline Weinrib, Laetitia Hoenberg / Nov. 18 - Dec. 6, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 942)
      Contents: 4 photos, 1 catalog
    - Artist/Event: Ann Sperry / March 4-22, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 943)
      Contents: 19 photos
    - Artist/Event: A.I.R. Group Show, "A Composite Portrait: A.I.R. and the Women's Art Movement Archives" / Jan. 2 - Jan. 18, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 944)
      Contents: 35 slides, 10 photocopies, 51 photos
      Photo credit: Daria Dorosh, Bob Gervais
    - Artist/Event: Carol Ross, Andrea Legge, "Fear of Flying" / Oct. 1 - Oct. 19, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 945)
      Contents: 6 photocopies
    - Artist/Event: MCAF Show: "Force of Habit" -- Curator: Alissa Schoenfeld / July 9 - July 27, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 946)
      Contents: 9 slides
    - Artist/Event: 2nd Biennial Exhibition -- Charlotta Kotik: Curator / May 28 - June 15, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 947)
      Contents: 1 postcard, 2 photos, 3 photonegatives, 33 slides
      Photo credit: Kay Canavino
    - Artist/Event:"Members Choice: Emerging Women Artists at A.I.R." July 11 - July 29, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 948)
    - Artist/Event: Jessie Nebraska Gifford, Ivy Dachman, Jan. 23 - Feb. 10, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 949)
    - Artist/Event: Diyan Achjadi (Box 20, Folder 950)
      Contents: 47 slides, 1 outslip: "Diyan Achjadi"
    - Artist/Event: Sheila Manion Artz (Box 20, Folder 951)
    - Artist/Event: Sharon Brant (Box 20, Folder 952)
    - Artist/Event: Faith Wilding (Box 20, Folder 953)
    - Artist/Event: Ann Wilson (Box 20, Folder 954)
  - Subseries R: C-I SLIDE SHOW
    - Artist/Event: A.I.R. Gallery Curated Slide Show Series by Art Critic Donald Kuspit (Box 20, Folder 955)
      Old number: C - I - 1 - (1- )
      Contents: 37 slides, 1 outslip: "Nancy Spero Codex Artaud", 1 list of contents
    - Artist/Event: A.I.R. Gallery Curated Slide Show Series by Art Critic Lucy Lippard (Box 20, Folder 956)
      Old number: C - I - 2 - (1- )
      Contents: 19 slides, 1 outslip: "May Stevens Mysteries and Politics 1998", 1 list of contents
    - Artist/Event: A.I.R. Gallery Curated Slide Show Series by Art Critic Kay Larson (Box 20, Folder 957)
      Old number: C - I - 3 - (1- )
      Contents: 78 slides, 1 list of contents
    - Artist/Event: A.I.R. Invitational May 28 - June 28, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 958)
      Old number: C - I - 4
      Photo credit: W.B. Nickerson; Linda Rubinstein
  - Subseries S: C-II
    - Artist/Event: Nancy White (Box 20, Folder 959)
      Old number: 67
      Contents: 1 postcard, 59 slides
    - Artist/Event: Jan. 4 - Jan. 22, 1994 Members Show / Patricia Smith (Box 20, Folder 960)
      Contents: 1 postcard, 1 catalog
    - Artist/Event: October 26 - Nov. 13, 1993 / "Women About Art: The Turnaround Year" (Juried Show) (Box 20, Folder 961)
      Contents: 1 postcard, 46 slides, 14 photos, 4 photonegatives
    - Artist/Event: Barbara Roux (Box 21, Folder 962)
      Contents: 1 photo, 4 photocopies
    - Artist/Event: Macro Micro / June 22 - July 24, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 963)
      Contents: 30 slides
    - Artist/Event: Fellowship/E. Zechel / June 1 - 19, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 964)
    - Artist/Event: Oct. 20 - Nov. 7, 1998 / Louise McCagg, Katinka Mann (Box 21, Folder 965)
      Old number:#52
      Contents: 3 photos, 4 postcards
    - Artist/Event: Sept. 29 - Oct. 17, 1998 / Carol Kreeger Davidson, Hilary Lorenz (Box 21, Folder 966)
    - Artist/Event: April 21 - May 9, 1998 / Daria Dorosh: Scraps and Shadows, Elizabeth Hill: A Biography (Box 21, Folder 967)
      Contents: 11 photocopies, 9 slides, 4 photos
    - Artist/Event: Jan. 6 - 24, 1998 / Currents Digital Art Show (Box 21, Folder 968)
      Contents: 18 slides, 15 photocopies
    - Artist/Event: Oct. 21 - Nov. 15, 1997 / The Generations Show: Celebrating the 25th Anniversary (Box 21, Folder 969)
      Contents: 1 envelope with 18 photos (+ negatives), 1 envelope with 3 photos, 1 envelope with photonegative strip, 1 envelope with 12 slides
  - Subseries T: C-III
    - Artist/Event: n/a (Box 21, Folder 970)
      Contents: entire contents of binder: 8 photos, 3 slides, 1 paper: "Stephanie Bernheim Color Wars '93 installation"
  - Subseries U: Misc. photos/slides
    - Artist/Event: Photos lent to Julie Ault for Alternative Art New York 1965-1985 (A.I.R. Gallery Members + Events -- 97 Wooster St.) (Box 21, Folder 971)
      Photo credit: A.I.R. Gallery
    - Artist/Event: Misc. photos (63 Crosby St. opening, Carolee Schneemann, Howardena Pindell 1973 exhibition, "Choice" exhibition[?]) (Box 21, Folder 972)
      Contents: 13 photos, 4 contact sheets, misc. paper files (inc. correspondence and photocopies)
      Photo credit: Maude Boltz, Jim Allison, Mary Beth Edelson
    - Artist/Event: Misc. photos (A.I.R. Gallery installation/sculpture show 1985, "Women Artists of the '80s: New Talent"[?] artists inc. Joan Snitzer and Susan Bee) (Box 21, Folder 973)
      Contents: 15 photos, 1 contact sheet, 8 photonegative strips, misc. paper)
      Photo credit: D. James Dee, Mark Stern, Adam Reich, Bob Rubic
    - Artist/Event: Misc. photos (Unknown exhibition installation, "Choice" exhibition[?], "A.I.R. Members Exhibit 1985" contact sheets inc. Loretta Dunkelman and Donna Byars) (Box 21, Folder 974)
      Contents: 26 photos, 2 contact sheets, misc. correspondence
      Photo credit:"Thom"
    - Artist/Event: Misc. photos/slides (A.I.R. Member portrait ca. 1992[?], unknown panel discussion, "Choice" exhibition, "Cultural Economies" slides, Louise Kramer "Auschwitz Head" slide, Slide presentation, photos of various A.I.R. members) (Box 21, Folder 975)
      Contents: 17 photos, 13 slides, misc. paper (inc. photo print-out)
      Photo credit: David Pratke
    - Artist/Event: Misc. photos/slides ("Showing the Unacceptable," 63 Crosby St., Members slides, "Holiday A.I.R.," Artist and group show slides and photos inc. Daria Dorosh, Blythe Bohnen, Julia Shepley, Leila Daw (Box 21, Folder 976)
      Contents: 128 slides, 3 photos, 2 contact sheets, misc. paper (inc. correspondence)
      Photo credit: Paula Barr; Mary Beth Edelson
    - Artist/Event: Misc. slides (Gallery members, Emerging Artists) (Box 21, Folder 977)
      Contents: 242 + 1 outslip, misc. paper (inc. correspondence)
    - Artist/Event: Misc. slides ("Force of Habit" exhibition, former Gallery members, A.I.R. slide checklist, Crosby St. gallery space, Oct. 1985 group show, misc. shows and artists, inc. Nancy Spero, "Choice," National Affiliates 1995) (Box 21, Folder 978)
      Contents: 161 slides, 12 outslips, 1 slide checklist
    - Artist/Event: Misc. photonegatives (unknown exhibitions) (Box 21, Folder 979)
      Contents: 24 photonegative strips
  - Subseries V: Slide Registry A-K
    - Slide Registry A-J (Box 22)
      Includes slides by: Lorna Bieber, May Castleberry, Petah Coyne, Elisa d'Arrigo, Jane Ellen Gilmor, Marcia Godosky, Coco Gordon, Donna Henes
      Contents: 383 slides
    - Slide Registry K-R (Box 23)
      Includes slides by: Ursula Kavanagh, Barbara Klein, Mary Ellen Long, Irene R. Mikol, Anna Poor, Beatrice Riese, Marilyn R. Rosenberg
      Contents: 261 slides
    - Slide Registry S-Z (Box 24)
      Includes slides by: Ceevah Sobel, Esther Solondz, April Vollmer, Joan Weber, Jean Kondo Weigl, Faith Wilding
      Contents: 193 slides
- Series V: Sound recordings
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains audio recordings of gallery lectures, panel discussions, readings and other events that have taken place at A.I.R..
  Conditions Governing Access
  Access copies for some materials are available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Please contact fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
  - A.I.R. Gallery, Women Artists: Political Attitudes, Dub No. 3, April 23, 1983; ID:184.0001 (Box 25, Media ID:184.0001, Box Shared Fales 146, Cd 184.0001)
    Original format: Audiocassette, TDK D90
    Duration: 02 minutes
    Existence and Location of Copies
    CD access copy available.
    Currently available.
  - A.I.R. Gallery, The Cultural Construction of Gender, Dub: 1 of 2, December 4, 1983; ID: 184.0002 (Box 25, Media ID: 184.0002, Box Shared Fales 146, Cd 184.0002_pt.1, Cd 184.0002_pt.2)
    CD access copy available. Please request Part I and Part II.
    Original format: Audiocassette, Sony LNX 90
    Duration: 94 minutes
  - A.I.R. Gallery, The Cultural Construction of Gender, Dub: 3, December 4, 1984; ID: 184.0003 (Box 25, Media ID: 184.0003, Box Shared Fales 146, Cd 184.0003)
    Original format: Audiocassette, Sony CHF 90
    Duration: 48 minutes
  - A.I.R. Poets: Kate Daniels, Paula Jean Hoffman, Suzanne McConnell, Original 1 + 2, November 11, 1984; ID: 184.0004 (Box 25, Media ID: 184.0004, Box Shared Fales 146, Cd 184.0004)
    Original format: Audiocassette, Sony CHF 90, contents described on tape as: "Kate Daniels, Paula Jean Hoffman, Suzanne McConnell Poets"
    Duration: 73 minutes
  - A.I.R. Poets: Kate Daniels, Paula Jean Hoffman, Suzanne McConnell, Original 3, Novermber 11, 1984; ID: 184.0005 (Box 25, Media ID: 184.0005, Box Shared Fales 146, Cd 184.0005)
    Duration: 74 minutes
  - Joanna Isaak and Jeff Kipnis at A.I.R.- Original, 1 + 2, November 18, 1984; ID: 184.0006 (Box 25, Media ID: 184.0006, Box Shared Fales 146, Cd 184.0006_pt.1, Cd 184.0006_pt.2)
    Duration: 92 minutes
  - Joanna Isaak and Jeff Kipnis at A.I.R.- Original, 3, November 18, 1984; ID: 184.0007 (Box 25, Media ID: 184.0007, Box Shared Fales 146, Cd 184.0007)
    Duration: 19 minutes
  - Joanna Isaak and Jeff Kipnis at A.I.R.- Dub, 1 + 2, November 18, 1984; ID: 184.0008 (Box 25, Media ID: 184.0008)
    Currently unavailable until duplication occurs.
  - Joanna Isaak and Jeff Kipnis at A.I.R.- Dub, 3, November 18, 1984; 184.0009 (Box 25, Media 184.0009)
  - Joanna Isaak and Jeff Kipnis at A.I.R.- Dub, 3, November 18, 1984; ID: 184.0010 (Box 25, Media ID: 184.0010)
    Currently unavailable until duplication occurs..
  - Women in Limbo Panel, February 9, 1991; ID: 184.0011 (Box 25, Media ID: 184.0011, Box Shared Fales 146, Cd 184.0011_pt.1, Cd 184.0011_pt.2)
    Original format: Audiocassette, Maxell XLII-S 90
    Duration: 84 minutes
  - A.I.R. Panel: Who Cares About Feminism: Art + Politics in the 1990s; sides 1 + 2, November 14, 1991; ID: 184.0012 (Box 25, Media ID: 184.0012)
    Original format: Audiocassette, Rezound Copy Cassette C-63
  - A.I.R. Panel: Who Cares About Feminism: Art + Politics in the 1990s; sides 1 + 2, November 14, 1991; ID: 184.0013 (Box 25, Media ID: 184.0013, Box Shared Fales 146, Cd 184.0013_pt.1, Cd 184.0013_pt.2)
    Duration: 93 minutes
  - A.I.R. Panel: Who Cares About Feminism: Art + Politics in the 1990s; sides 1 + 2, November 14, 1991; ID: 184.0014 (Box 25, Media ID: 184.0014)
  - A.I.R. Panel: Who Cares About Feminism: Art + Politics in the 1990s; sides 3 + 4, November 14, 1991; ID: 184.0015 (Box 25, Media ID: 184.0015, Box Shared Fales 145, Cd 184.0015)
    Duration: 20 minutes
  - A.I.R. Panel: Who Cares About Feminism: Art + Politics in the 1990s; sides 3 + 4, November 14, 1991; ID: 184.0016 (Box 25, Media ID: 184.0016)
  - A.I.R. Panel: Who Cares About Feminism: Art + Politics in the 1990s; sides 3 + 4, November 14, 1991; ID: 184.0017 (Box 25, Media ID: 184.0017)
  - Who Cares About Feminism: Art + Politics in the 1990s; A.I.R. Gallery, tape I, November 14, 1991; ID: 184.0018 (Box 25, Media ID: 184.0018, Box Shared Fales 145, Cd 184.0018_pt.1, Cd 184.0018_pt.2)
    Original format: Audiocassette, Maxell XLII-S 90; contains sticker with "Stephanie Bernheim 50 Walker St. 4A New York, NY 10013"; see also 184.0018A for paper material associated with cassette
  - Who Cares About Feminism: Art + Politics in the 1990s; A.I.R. Gallery, tape II, November 14, 1991; ID: 184.0019 (Box 25, Media ID: 184.0019, Box Shared Fales 145, Cd 184.0019)
    Original format: Audiocassette, Maxell XLII-S 90; contains sticker with "Stephanie Bernheim 50 Walker St. 4A New York, NY 10013"
  - Who Cares About Feminism; A.I.R. Gallery, tape I, November 14, 1991; ID: 184.0020 (Box 25, Media ID: 184.0020)
    Original format: Audiocassette, Sony HF 90
  - Who Cares About Feminism; A.I.R. Gallery, tape II, November 14, 1991; ID: 184.0021 (Box 25, Media ID: 184.0021)
  - A.I.R. Workshop: "Feminism: Theory in/and Practice"; tape 1, April 5, 1995; ID: 184.0022 (Box 25, Media ID: 184.0022, Box Shared Fales 145, Cd 184.0022)
    Original format: Audiocassette, TDK D60, labeled as Master
    Duration: 63 minutes
  - A.I.R. Workshop: "Feminism: Theory in/and Practice"; tape 2, April 5, 1995; ID: 184.0023 (Box 25, Media ID: 184.0023, Box Shared Fales 145, Cd 184.0023)
    Duration: 40 minutes
  - A.I.R.: The Early Years, March 19, 1996; ID: 184.0024 (Box 25, Media ID: 184.0024)
    Original format: Microcassette, Sony MC-90
  - A.I.R.: The Early Years, March 19, 1996; ID: 184.0025 (Box 25, Media ID: 184.0025, Box Shared Fales 145, Cd 184.0025)
    Original format: Audiocassette, Sony/Sadler Recording Studio Inc.; spine labeled "Fishbone - In the Cube (Deep Doo Doo)"
    Duration: 77 minutes
  - What Happened to WAC?: A.I.R., November 4, 1997; ID: 184.0027 (Box 25, Media ID: 184.0027)
    Original format: Audiocassette, Maxell XL II-90
  - Women and Abstraction, November 21, 1997; ID: 184.0028 (Box 25, Media ID: 184.0028, Box Shared Fales 145, Cd 184.0028)
    Duration: 47 minutes
  - Exec. Comm. Meeting, March 15, 1998; ID: 184.0029 (Box 25, Media ID: 184.0029, Box Shared Fales 145, Cd 184.0029_pt.1, Cd 184.0029_pt.2)
    Original format: Audiocassette, TDK SA-X100
    Duration: 105 minutes
  - 3rd Biennial Gallery Talk: E. Sussman, December 3, 1998; ID: 184.0030 (Box 25, Media ID: 184.0030, Box Shared Fales 145, Cd 184.0030)
    Original format: Audiocassette, TDK D-120 (housed in Maxell X L-II S case); typed on inner cassette label: "Sylvia Netzer Ceramics 1999"
    Duration: 59 minutes
- Series VI: Video recordings
  Scope and Content